(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T20:52:34.320218",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
YouTube Music Weekend をご覧の皆さん、
Hello everyone watching YouTube Music Weekend!
こんにちは！
Hello!
初めまして！
Nice to meet you!
ホロライブデバイスのReGLOSSです。
We are Hololive Device's ReGLOSS!
一人ずつ自己紹介からいきたいと思います。
We'd like to introduce ourselves one by one!
スタート！
Start!
ホロライブデバイス所属ReGLOSSの、
From Hololive Device ReGLOSS, playing music,
音楽の、音乃瀬奏だよ！
It's Kanade Kanade!
そして！ホロライブデバイスReGLOSSの一条莉々華よ、みんなヤッホー元気？
And from Hololive Device ReGLOSS, Ichijou Ririka!
みんなヤッホー元気？
Hello everyone, are you doing well?
元気だよー！
Doing great!
はい皆さんこんにちは！ホロライブデバイスはReGLOSSのにぎやかスネーク担当1511もんわ…全然違いない！
And hello everyone, from Hololive Device ReGLOSS, Ichijou Ririka... wait, no!
まいどけぐるの…お姉さんこと音瀬ラデンでございます。
It's Otonase Kanade!
どうも！まいどけまいどけぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐると…！
And yes, it's Otonase Kanade!
いや昨年に続き今年もYouTube Music Weekendに参加させていただけてとっても光栄です！
We're so happy to be participating in YouTube Music Weekend again this year!
ちょっと天狗にしてね。
Too happy...
今行くからね、今見に行けるかなって思っちゃった。
I thought we could go see it!
じゃあもう一回！わかんない。うん、ふう。
Let's try that again!
年に引き続き今年もYouTube Music Weekendに参加させていただけて光栄です！
We're so happy to be participating in YouTube Music Weekend again this year!
え、みんな去年さん何の曲やったか覚えてる？
Hey everyone, do you remember what song you did last year?
シンメトリー！
Shimetrie!
あ、シンメトリーやったね。
Ah, Shimetrie!
絶対やったよ！デビュー曲だもんね。
We definitely did Shimetrie because it was our debut song!
うん。そしてもう一曲やってて、当時のね、新曲である「Hutakado Maybe」も披露させていただきました！
And we also released our new song at the time, "Hutakado Maybe"!
懐かしい！
Nostalgic!
ね、本当懐かしいね。
It really is nostalgic!
すごいもう、超昔のことのようにも思えるし、当時はね、やっぱこういうステージに立つわけじゃなくって、
It feels like it was ages ago, but at the time, we weren't really standing on stages like this...
こう、なんていうかさ、あの、こう周り、今見てこれ、すごい！
We were just around, and look at this!
すごい人がいる！すごい！ありがたい！
There are so many people!
ちょっとみんなしんとしたいで。
Don't get too emotional, everyone!
でも画面の向こうで今めちゃめちゃ盛り上がってくれてると思って。めちゃめちゃ増えてるんだよ。
It's getting super lively on the other side of the screen!
増えたんだよ。
It increased so much!
すごいね、カメラとかステージとかも進化して再び戻ってきちゃいました！
The cameras and stages have evolved and we're back again!
実はね、昨年から楽曲も増えまして、
Actually, since last year, we've had more songs!
今年はね、3月に「サクラミラージュ」、7月に「ミッドサマーナイト」という曲をですね、リリースしてあります！あります！
This year we released "Sakura Mirage" in March and "Midsummer Night" in July!
いや、全く今年もこうして新しい曲をみんなに披露することができて、嬉しいね！ねえ、嬉しい！
So we're so happy to be able to showcase our new songs to everyone this year too!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
そしてそして、実は8月に、なんと！
And actually, in August...
かなでたちのソロ曲を毎週連続リリースしてました！
We released our solo songs every single week!
ラでちゃんから！
Starting with Rade-chan!
はい、ラでです。ええ、ラでんのソロ曲「落とし話」リリースさせていただきました。なんと語り合い、言葉遊び、ランプありと、
Yes, it's Raden! My solo song is called "Otoshi Banashi", and it was released!
ええ、
And...
ラでんらしさをね、ぎゅっと詰め込んだ楽曲となっております。そしてね、実はこの要素もね、どっかにね、どっかにね、あったりするんです！気づかなかった…ええ？あるんですね、実は！ちょっと探して聞いてみようかな。
Raden-ness is crammed into this song!
ぜひ「落とし話」よろしくお願いします。
So please look forward to "Otoshi Banashi"!
そしてラデンの次の週にリリースしたのが誰だ？
And who released their song the week after Raden?
かなで！発音が良すぎて、なんで？なんで？なんで言ったの？
Kanade! Wait, why did you say it like that?
「Yofuru Vibes Echo」っていう楽曲をリリースしました！
We released a song called "Yofuru Vibes Echo"!
こちらの楽曲はですね、ちょっと、あかりがじゃんじゃがじゃんじゃがじゃんじゃがする感じの曲で、なんかすごい、ね、しっとりとした曲で、
This song has a chill vibe, like "janjan-gajanjan",
朝とかに起きて聞くと、はあ、今日も一日あさだ、頑張ろうってなる、曲はね、あの、作らせていただきまして、
If you listen to it when you wake up in the morning, you'll think, "Ah, I'll do my best today too!"
かなでもすごいニコニコしながら歌ったので、元気が出る、そういう楽曲になっています！よかったら聞いてね！
Kanade sang it with a big smile, so it's a song that gives you energy!
聞いてね！
Listen to it!
そしてかなでの次は誰だ？りのの楽曲！
And who's next after Kanade?
タイトルの「ハピネスフェノメノン」！おお！
It's Ririka's song! The title is "Happiness Phenomenon"!
その、いい女がもう全身から溢れ出せちゃうような、そんな楽曲になっていて、もう聴くだけで気分あげあげ、自己肯定感あげあげな楽曲となってます！わあ！
It's a song where a good woman overflows from head to toe, and just listening to it boosts your mood and self-confidence!
朝とかお昼とか、これから頑張るぞみたいなときに聴いてね、一緒に元気を出してもらえたらいいなと思っております！た、聴いてね！
So when you listen to it in the morning or at lunch, I hope it gives you energy together!
聞いて聞いて！
Hello! Hello!
そして？
And then,
最後は、聴き始めの初曲、
lastly, our very first solo song,
「BD Bi-Li-Ra」でしちゃ！
"BD, Bi, Li, Ra" is here!
ソロ曲なんですけど、あの、まず男臭...
It's a solo song, but first...
ダンスナンバー？
dance number?
で、こう、ドゥーン、ドゥーンって、低音がこう、ドゥーン、ドゥーンってなってて、
It's got that "dun, dun" low bass...
なんかこう、シャビに音数じゃちょっと少なくないんだけど、
It's not super loud,
静かな静寂の中で、
but within that quiet tranquility...
あ、なんかノートブ感の、なんか始め結構普段ダウンナーなんだけど、
it has kind of a notes vibe,
その夜の、ちょっとダウンナーな静かな感じと、その、低音のガーン、ガーンっていう、
with that low bass "gun, gun" cool vibe,
かっこよさが合わさった曲になってて、
it's a really cool song,
なんか、しょ、ちょっと、夜に、ちょっと、はっ、ふっ。
so if you listen at night,
もう、聴いて、一人で聴いてほしいなって、
you'll want to get lost in it alone.
ラップとかダンスブレイクもあって、
It has rap tracks and dance breaks too,
あの、しょ、かっこいい曲になってるので、ぜひぜひ聴いてください！
so please definitely go listen to this cool song!
なんかね、実はあれなんだよね、
Actually, did you know?
ソロ曲それぞれ、時間帯が変わっていくんだよね。
Each solo song's time of day changes!
奏のが、朝！
Kanade's is early morning,
莉々華の、昼！
Ririka's is midday,
初芽、夜。
Hajime's is night...
そう。
So,
だからね、ぜひあの、この順に聴くとね、
if you listen to them in this order,
ちょっとさらに、神なんじゃないかな、なんて思っております。
it tells a story, don't you think?
ま、という感じでね、それぞれReGLOSSの皆の個性がたっぷり詰まった楽曲になっているので、
So with that, each of our ReGLOSS personalities is packed into these songs,
気になっていただけたら、なんと概要欄にね、リンクが貼ってありますので、
so if you're curious, the link is in the description box,
そちらもぜひ聴いてみてください！
so please definitely go listen to them!
え、もう、なんか、MC流げよって、もしかしたら今思われてるかもしれないけど、
You might think, "Are you guys dropping an MC?"
ちょっと待って、ちょ、もうちょっとだけ喋らせてね、あの、そのあとすぐに歌いますんでね。
Hold on, wait just a bit longer and we'll sing right after!
あとちょっと、あとちょっとね。
Hold on, wait just a bit!
いや、しかもですね、実は私たち、今年の9月でなんと、
And what's more, actually, us...
デビュー2周年を、迎えます！
Debut 2nd Anniversary!
嘘！
No way!
そうなんだよ、しかも、デビュー2周年を迎えるということは、
So, celebrating our 2nd anniversary means...
お、何？3Dの記念配信もあるということー！
there'll be a 3D anniversary live stream too!
初めて聞いた！
We're hearing about this for the first time!
なんで？
What?
9月13日(土) 20時「ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary」ReGLOSS 公式チャンネルにて配信
A 3D anniversary stream will be held on Saturday, September 13th at 20:00!
何するの？まあ、やっぱり、歌ったり踊ったりしちゃうんじゃない？
What are we gonna do? Well, naturally...
漫才じゃないんですか？
Isn't this a comedy skit?
あの、漫才だけが踊る。
Just the manzai part is dancing?
なんでみんなで踊って歌っちゃおうよ。え、どうしようかな？
Why is everyone dancing and singing?
なんでみんな驚いとるんだよ。え、やるの？ってなんでだっての。
Why are you all surprised?
やるのかなと思って、
I thought maybe we should do that,
漫才だと思って、なんちゃって思っちゃったんだ。
so I thought it's manzai.
いや、でもね、漫才とかじゃないよ。冗談は置いておきつつ、
Well, jokes aside,
そう、この2年間ね、みんなにこうやって見てもらうために、たくさん練習も重ねてきたので、
for the past 2 years, we've practiced a lot so everyone could see us like this,
さらに去年よりもさらにパワーアップした姿をみんなにお見せできたらなと思っております！
and we hope to show an even more powered-up version of ourselves compared to last year!
イェーイ！
Yay!
え、ちなみにさ、もうこの1年でさ、なんか変わったこととかある？
By the way, have you guys changed at all in this past year?
うわ、変わったこと？
Anything?
顔も顔が変わったけどね。
Even our faces changed?
なにもかも？なにもかも？
What? What?
え、変わったのはあってさ。
Well, the songs changed, right?
まあ、レッスンとか、なんか
Like, for lessons,
こう初めて3Dライブ1周年のときにあってさ、なんか、踊りながら歌うのって大変だなってすごい思ったの。歌、こう立って歌うのだったらすごい得意なのかなって思ってたけど、
when we did our 1st 3D live, I thought, "Dancing and singing at the same time is so hard,"
いざこう体を動かしながら歌うってなると、なんかこう息が上がっちゃって、
but once you start moving your body while singing,
難しいなってなっちゃって、そこからさ、ボイトレとかダンスレッスンとかを増やしてね、
it gets so hard, so we increased our vocal training and dance lessons,
体裁は実はかなり発声が変わりました！
and our stamina has actually changed a lot!
おー！
Wow!
もう最初からあんなに綺麗に歌わしらだったのに、
We weren't even able to sing this cleanly from the start,
よりグレードアップしたってことだよね。
so that means we've grade-upped!
イェーイ！
Yay!
よかったらね、見比べてみたりして見てください。
So if you compare us, please take a look!
これからも進化するぞー！
We'll keep evolving from here on!
音柱、音柱じゃねえや、歌柱。歌柱だよ。
Look at that pillar of sound... wait, pillar of song!
やばい、やばい、最初からやばい、もう出れなくなっちゃった。
Oh no, I messed up right at the beginning!
いや、初めもソロ、あの新しいジャンル
Well, for solo songs,
をずっと、なんか、入手しちゃいなって思ってたんだけど、
we've always wanted to try,
それをね、今年、2つ挑戦してて、1つは、まあ言っててタップなんだけど、
and this year we challenged ourselves to two of them—tap, you know?
でもう1個もね、あの別のジャンルを初めて見たりしてて、
And the other was trying out a completely different genre,
そう、なんか全然違うから、もう本当ゼロからのスタートみたいな感じなの。
so they're totally different, feeling like starting completely from zero.
そうだから、これをやってて、またなんかこう、じゃあ3Dライブとかで披露できる機会があったら、なんかまた進化した姿を見られるんじゃないかなって思ってさ。
So we've been doing that, and if there's a chance to shine during a 3D live, I hope you'll see our evolved forms!
楽しみ、3Dライブ！
So please look forward to it!
うん、いいね。
Yeah!
じゃあ2人はもう得意なことをさらにまたグレードアッ
So both of us took what we're good at and grade-upped...
ことというか、まあ進めていくような感じでがんばってるってことだよね。
Meaning, we've been working hard to keep moving forward, right?
はい、りりかは
Yes, and as for Ririka—
あの、ちょっと心が変わりなって思ってることがあって、
Well, my mindset has shifted a bit recently.
最初本当にちょっとダンスが特に苦手すぎて、こういうライブとかみんなの前で踊るみたいなときに緊張だったりとか不安だったりとかいっぱいあったんだけど
At first, I was really bad at dancing, so whenever I had a live or had to dance in front of everyone, I felt so much nervousness and anxiety.
ま、今回は、
But this time,
とある曲を、ま、踊らせていただいて、歌わせていただいたんですけど、
we got to dance and sing a certain song,
それをとったときに、なんか不安だって気持ちより、一緒にやってて楽しいなっていう気持ちの方が、なんかあった気がして、
and when we filmed it, rather than feeling anxious, I felt more of a sense of joy and fun doing it together.
えー！すごい！えー、素敵！奥さん、素敵よ、あなた！
Wow, amazing! That's wonderful! You're wonderful, my friend!
え、それ聞けたらこっちもうれしいよね。よかった！
If we hear that, it makes us happy too. I'm so glad!
だからこれからもいっぱい歌って踊って、レッスンもがんばっていきたいと思います！
So I want to keep singing, dancing, and working hard at lessons from now on!
がんばろ！がんばろ！がんばろ！
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
ではでちゃんは、と、ラデンさ、うん、
Next is Ao-chan... Raden-san, yeah.
作詞にハマってさ、この1年で、で、自分てね、そう特にラップ、なんか、やっぱね、言葉が好きなので、特に日本語が好きで、
I got into writing lyrics this past year, and as myself—especially rap—I really love words, especially the Japanese language.
で、それでちょっと何かやりたいなと思って、自作のラップ書いて、自分のチャンネルに投稿したりとか、
So wanting to do something with that, I wrote my own rap and posted it on my channel,
ね、素敵だったよね、私たちの名前とかも入れてくれて
and it was wonderful, she even included our names in it!
早口言葉、早口言葉がいっぱい。
Lots of tongue twisters, so many tongue twisters!
そう、なんかそういうね、言葉と音楽みたいなところで、なんか自分に新しい挑戦ができたかなという1年でしたね！
Yeah, so it was a year where I felt I could take on new challenges combining words and music!
もうみんなそれぞれにね、成長と挑戦を重ねた1年でございましたと。
It's been a year where everyone has accumulated growth and challenges respectively.
でもありまだまだね、伸びしろもあるし、成長できる部分いっぱいあると思うから、これからもがんばってこね！
But there's still room to grow and so many areas to improve, so let's keep doing our best from here on!
はい、ということで今回は先日発表されました、私たちReGLOSSの新曲「MIDDLESUMMERSTRUT」をこのあと披露させていただきます！
Yes, so today we will be performing our new ReGLOSS song "MIDDLESUMMERSTRUT" which was recently announced!
3月にリリースした「サクラミラージュ」は春の訪れを感じられる楽曲だったと思いますが、今回の「MIDDLESUMMERSTRUT」は、タイトル通り、タイトル通り
While "Sakura Mirage" released in March was a song where you could feel the arrival of spring, this time "MIDDLESUMMERSTRUT", true to its title—true to its title—
なつ！なつ！あつ！
Summer! Summer! Hot!
あ、ちも今これステージ立ってるけど、日陰とかないからさ、
Ah, and even though we're standing on stage right now, there's no shade, so...
ね、日焼けやばいって！
Right, sunburn is no joke!
ここにいるってことはさ、夏と一緒にここに帰ってきたっていう感じするよね！
Being here makes it feel like we came back here together with summer!
なんか爽やかなメロディーとね、心地よいリズムが夏の暑さを吹き飛ばしてくれるような1曲になってます。
It's a song where the refreshing melody and pleasant rhythm blow away the summer heat.
で、みんなこの曲のイメージとか、なんかレコーディングのエピソードとかある？
So, does anyone have any impressions of this song or recording episodes?
はい！やっぱ夏だしすごい爽やかな曲だから、明るく楽しく爽やかにっていうのをすごいイメージしながら歌ったの覚えてる。
Yes! Since it's summer and a very refreshing song, I remember singing it with a strong image of being bright, fun, and refreshing.
確かにそんな感じだった。本当？うん、感じた感じた！やったー！
It really felt like that. Really? Yeah, we felt it! Yay!
はい、この楽曲のサビに、踊ってミッドサマー！っていうフレーズがあるんだけど、ま、歌うまっ
Yes, in the chorus of this song, there's a phrase "Dance, Midsummer!", but singing it well—
自分の歌うまっ！ありがとう！すっごい歌うまっ！
"Singing it well!" Thank you! You sing so well!
そのサマをさ、かなりすごいリズムノリノリに乗るの好きだから、踊ってミッドサマー！ってやってて、サマサマ、サマサマになりすぎちゃって、サマサマってやってて
For "summer", I love getting really into the groove, so for "Dance, Midsummer!", I got too carried away with "summer summer", going "summer summer"—
ディレクターさんにね、お歌をこうやってくれるディレクターさんに、いやちょっとサマ過ぎるんで、ちょっと、やって歌ってくださいて笑われたんだよね。
The director, who helps us with singing, laughed and told me, "Um, it's a bit too much 'summer', so could you tone it down a bit?"
調整して歌ったのを覚えてます。めちゃいいエピソードあるやん。
I remember adjusting and singing it. That's such a great episode.
えー、初め振り付けで試験あったことがあって、やっぱサビの皆しきやって思うけどさ、こうで、あ、そうかね、これ難しい。
Um, we had a dance test at first, and for the chorus everyone thought—like this, oh right, this is hard.
あの、のっき、ギコギコって覚えてる。ヒモでギコギコ。あ、なるほどね、そう。ギコギコ、ギコギコね。
Um, Nokki, "creaky creaky", remember? Creaky with a string. Ah, I see, right. Creaky creaky, creaky creaky.
これが楽しこってめっちゃすっきやねん。気持ちいいもんね、ここなんか、バチっとハマるよね。
This is fun, I love it so much. It feels so good, it just clicks into place.
え、ラデンちゃんはどう？
And Raden-chan, how about you?
いっぱい練習しました、聞いてください！ダンスも歌もとにかく大変でした、聞いてください！やっぱそこだよね、わかる！いっぱい聞いてください！
I practiced a lot, please listen to it! Dancing and singing was so hard, please listen to it! That's right, I get it! Please listen to it a lot!
はい、じゃあね、そんなミッドサマーシトラス、このあとみんなに見てもらうと思うけど
Yes, so, about that "Midsummer Citrus", we want everyone to watch it after this, but—
もう早く見てもらいたいよね！
We want you to see it already!
そろそろね、そろそろね、エムシーだいぶ長くなっちゃったからね
Well, it's about time, since the MC has gotten pretty long...
じゃんけんぽん！あわせてほい！
Rock, paper, scissors! Show me what you've got!
Rock, paper, scissors! Show me!
やったー！よっしゃ！やったー！いぇい！
Yay! Alright! Yay! Yeah!
灼き付くような陽射し 水面に浮かぶスパークール
Scorching sunlight, sparkles floating on the water's surface.
燻る夏色と逆光の裏側で あの日の青春を呼び起こしてる
Behind smoldering summer colors and backlight, calling back our youth.
デニムの裾を捲って 裸足で走ってる砂の上
Rolling up denim hems, running barefoot on the sand.
硝子の縁で 回り回る 輝く 瑠璃色のビー玉
Spinning round and round on the edge of glass, a shining lapis lazuli marble.
なんだか、その笑顔と紙一重だ
Somehow, it's a hair's breadth away from that smile.
フィルムを覗けば ノンフィクション 彩りに縛られた メモリー
Peeking through the film, non-fiction memories bound in colors.
リセットなんて 出来ない から
Because you can't just reset it all.
love yourself just as you are now
踊って ミッドサマー アルゴリズム の 中
Dancing in the midsummer algorithm
瞬時で ダブリング して
Doubling in an instant.
切り取って 喜怒哀楽 これが きっと 愛 だ
Capturing all emotions—surely this is love.
二度と 忘れない よう に
So we'll never forget it.
le lemon lime orange
Lemon, lime, orange.
キミ と 一生分 の 思い出
A lifetime's worth of memories with you.
何気ない 一 日 が one of a kind
Every ordinary day is one of a kind.
よし、ぐーぱっち！おじゃー！
Alright, rock paper scissors!
グッパで別れましょ！いぇーい！
Let's split with good-pa! Yay!
氷が溶けては渦巻いた 魔法の杖代わりのマドラー
Ice melted and swirled, a muddler acting as a magic wand.
喉の奥くすぐる炭酸 香る柑橘系のフレーバー
Carbonation tickling the back of the throat, fragrant citrus flavor.
爽やかな気流にのって 波の還りを見守っている beachside
Riding a refreshing airflow, watching waves return at the beachside.
あどけない面影に焦がれ 微かに触れそうな指先
Yearning for innocent silhouettes, fingertips almost touching faintly.
煌めきで上塗りをしてしまおう
Let's coat it all over with sparkle.
get ahead of what you used to be
踊って ミッドサマー アルゴリズム の 中
Dancing in the midsummer algorithm.
瞬時で ダブリング して
Doubling in an instant.
切り取って 喜怒哀楽 これが きっと 愛 だ
Capturing all emotions—surely this is love.
二度と 忘れない よう に
So we'll never forget it.
ミッドサマーシトラス oh yeah
Midsummer Citrus, oh yeah.
いつだって we got love !! okay
We always got love!! Okay.
満たされているだけで フィクションな心はまた実り
Just by being fulfilled, fictional hearts bear fruit once more.
寝起きの太陽も願ってもない燦々日和？
Is the waking sun also brilliant weather we couldn't ask for better?
白飛びしてしまうほど 眩しい の は 夏 の せい
Being so blindingly washed out—that's just because of summer.
踊って ミッドサマー アルゴリズム の 中
Dancing in the midsummer algorithm.
瞬時で ダブリング して
Doubling in an instant.
切り取って 喜怒哀楽 これが きっと 愛 だ
Capturing all emotions—surely this is love.
二度と 忘れない よう に
So we'll never forget it.
le lemon lime orange
Lemon, lime, orange.
キミ と 一生分 の 思い出
A lifetime's worth of memories with you.
何気ない 一 日 が one of a kind
Every ordinary day is one of a kind.